A Guide to the Delia McMahan Papers, 1975-1980
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Delia McMahan, Papers, 1975-1980
Library of Virginia
38828
.90 cubic feet (2 boxes)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Charles Scarlett, 17 November 1994.
Scope and Content Information
This accession contains the genealogical research files kept by Delia McMahan and Helen Lorraine for McMahan's publication, "Pioneer Familes." Information is included on the Allen, Bird (Byrd), Gannaway, Gregory, Love, Shepard, Wright, and Yancey families of Augusta, Botetourt, Buckingham, Cumberland, Essex, Louisa, Pittsylvania, Shenandoah, and Wythe Counties, Virginia; and Ohio and North Carolina. Included are abstracts of deeds and wills, tax and vital statistics records, correspondence, family group sheets, notes, and published sources. Also included are two copies of "Pioneer Families", revised in 1977 and 1978.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by family name, with correspondence, notebooks, and copies of the finished genealogical notes arranged to the rear.
Contents List
- Allen family (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Allen, Benjamin (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Allen, Davis (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Allen, Margaret (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bird family (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bird, Abraham (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bird, Andrew (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Gannaway family (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Gannaway, John (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Gregory, Isaac (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Gregory, John (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Gregory, William (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Hubbard, Robert (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Love family (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Love, Philip (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Love, William (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Shepard family (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Shepard, Burwell (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Shepard, Carroll (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Shepard, Lucy (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Shepard, Robert (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Shepard, Samuel (b. 1695) (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Shepard, Samuel (1730-1792) (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Shepard, Samuel (1762-1852) (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Shepard, William (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Shepard, William E. (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Williams, Bailey (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Wright family (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Wright, Ambrose (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Wright, Ann (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Wright, Archibald (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Wright, Benjamin (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Wright, Eliza (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Wright, George (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Wright, George II (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Wright, Griffin (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Wright, James (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Wright, John (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Wright, Richard (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Wright, Samuel (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Wright, Seymour (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Wright, Susanna (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Wright, Thomas (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Wright, William (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Yancey family (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Correspondence 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Notebooks (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Pioneer Families: McQueen, Williams, Goss, Bird (Byrd), Allen, Neely, Love, and Gannaway 1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Pioneer Familes: Goss, Quakers, Butcher, Allen, McQueen, Love, Neely, Townsend, Collins, park, Button, Gorton 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)